To honour the JVM settings for this build a single-use Daemon process will be forked. For more on this, please refer to https://docs.gradle.org/8.4/userguide/gradle_daemon.html#sec:disabling_the_daemon in the Gradle documentation.
Daemon will be stopped at the end of the build 

> Configure project :app
WARNING: The option setting 'android.overridePathCheck=true' is experimental.
The current default is 'false'.
